Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Capital District, 1936-2008; 5; 6.22 cubic ft.
  - Capital District, Remote Park and Ride Express Bus Service, A Study of Potential Corridors and Commuter Shed Market Area in the Capital District, Draft Report, 1980 June (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Capital District, Residents' Perception of Community Mental Health Center in the Tri-Cities Area, 1976 April (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Capital District, Re: Solid Waste Management Feasibility Study…, 1987 December (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Capital District, Rotterdam Area Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1968 February (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Capital District, Rotterdam Area Comprehensive Sewerage Study, Summary, 1968 February (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Capital District, Sewer and Water Facilities Analysis, 1970 July (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Capital District, Soil Map of Albany and Schenectady Counties, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Capital District, Soil Survey: Albany and Schenectady Counties, 1942 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Capital District, Some Comparative Charts on Criminal Justice System Albany, Rensselaer, Saratoga, Schenectady, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Capital District, Southeast Saratoga Transportation Study, [Summary Report Draft], 1979 November (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Capital District, The Status of Transportation in the Capital District, [Newspaper Supplement], 1979 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Capital District, A Study of Regional Planning: The Port of Albany, 1969 May (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Capital District, Summary of the Finding of the Land Use Inventory, NY Dept. of Transportation, 1969 October (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Capital District, Summary of Home Interview Survey Data, Capital District Transportation Study, 1970 September (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Capital District, Summary of Travel Inventory Data, 1968 April (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Capital District, Summary Proposed Rule Part 231: Major Facilities, 1978 December (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Capital District, Summer Programs and Camp Directory, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Capital District, Survey of the Potential for Non-Bus Transit Service in the Capital District, Draft Appendices, 1981 January (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Capital District, Survey of the Potential for Non-Bus Transit Service in the Capital District, Draft Technical Report, 1981 January (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Capital District, Tomorrow's Jobs-Tomorrow's Workers, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Capital District, Traffic Count Factoring Procedures, 1981 December (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Capital District, Transit Operations Technical Study Interim Report One: System Profile, 1973 October (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Capital District, Transit Operations Technical Study Interim Report Two: Public Attitudes and Opinions, 1973 December (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Capital District, Transit Operations Technical Study Interim Report Three: Adequacy of Service, 1974 March (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Capital District, Transit Service in the Capital District: The Choices Ahead, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Capital District, Transportation for the Elderly and Handicapped in the Capital District, 1980 October (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Capital District, Transportation Improvement Program 1977-82, 1977 June (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Capital District, Transportation Improvement Program 1980-85, 1980 February (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Capital District, Transportation Improvement Program 1994-99, 1994 July (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Capital District, The Transportation Plan Summary, 1971 November (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Capital District, Transportation Planning Workshop: Arterial Management Issues, Tools and Techniques, 1996 June (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Capital District, Transportation Systems Management Element, 1980 March (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Capital District, Unified Planning Work Program 1979-80, 1979 February (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Capital District, Unified Planning Work Program 1980-81, 1980 February (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Capital District, Unified Planning Work Program 1990-91, 1990 February (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Capital District, Water Resource of the Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Capital District, Wolf Road/Exit 3 Area Transportation System Study [Executive Summary], 1990 March (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Capital District, Wolf Rood Ridesharing Experience, 1981 August (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Capital District, Year 2000 Highway Capacity Needs in the Capital District and a Ten-Year Capacity and Mobility Plan, 1990 August (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Hudson River Corridor, Capital District Hudson River Corridor Study Preliminary In-House Reports: Population, Land Use, Employment Summary of Issues [Confidential], Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Hudson River Corridor, Capital District Hudson River Corridor Study: Preliminary Public Finance Report [Marked Confidential], Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Hudson River Corridor, Scenic and Recreational Development, Hudson Riverfront Arterial, 1970 June (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Recreation in the Capital District: A Regional Base Study for the Statewide Comprehensive Outdoor Recreation Plan, 1968 December (Oversized 1)
- Greater Region, 1934-1997; 6; 6.43 cubic ft.
  This series contains those Capital District Regional Planning Commission Records that pertain to plans for areas outside the four "home counties" of the Capital District (i.e., Albany, Rensselaer, Saratoga, and Schenectady Counties). There are a great many documents that deal with planning decisions within Adirondack Park, as well as others focused on the Catskills region and the Appalachian Mountains. There are also planning documents for areas within Columbia County, Fulton County, Greene County, and Montgomery County. There are a significant number of files pertaining to the Hudson River and the Mohawk Valley. Additionally, there are documents pertaining to the Lake George/Lake Champlain area, as well as a small number of documents covering Western New York and the New York City/New Jersey area.
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Goals Program, Final Report on the Community Workshops: A Summary of Public Comment and Discussion, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park Agency Act, As Amended Through the Close of the 1990 Legislative Session, 1991 March (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park Land Use and Development Plan, 1973 August (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park Land Use and Development Plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondacks Park Land Use and Development Plan Maps, 1972-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park Land Use and Development Plan and Recommendations for Implementation, 1973 March (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondacks Park Map, 1972 August (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park Preliminary … Private Land Use and Development Plan [Draft for Public Hearing Purposes], Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park State Land Master Plan, 1972 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adirondacks, Adirondack Park State Land Master Plan, 1979 April (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adirondacks, "APA Self Study - Law 'Sound' But 'Misunderstood', [Newspaper Clipping From Lake Placid News], 1976 March (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adirondacks, A Citizen's Guide to Adirondack Park Agency Land Use Regulations, 1979 January (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adirondacks, A Citizen's Guide to Adirondack Park Agency Land Use Regulations, 1980 January (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adirondacks, Citizen's Guide to Adirondack Rivers and Roads, 1986 March (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adirondacks, Comprehensive Report, Volume 1, Adirondack Park Agency, 1976 February (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adirondacks, Development in the Adirondack Park: Objectives and Guidelines for Planning and Review, 1976 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adirondacks, Development in the Adirondack Park- Objectives and Guidelines for Planning and Review, 1977 April (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adirondacks, Draft Revisions to the State Land Master Plan [Map], 1977 January (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Adirondacks, Financial Implementation, Technical Report 7, 1977 January (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Adirondacks, Forest, Minerals, Water and Air, Technical Report 3, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Adirondacks, The Future of Adirondack Park, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Adirondacks, Governor Mario M. Cuomo's Proposals for the Adirondacks, 1991 October (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Adirondacks, Hamlets of the Adirondacks: History, Preservation and Investment, 1984 March (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Adirondacks, Implementing the Adirondack Park Agency Act (executive Law, Article 27) … (Environmental Conservation Law, Article 15, Title 27), 1982 October (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Adirondacks, Local Government, Technical Report 6, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Adirondacks, Local Planning and Land Use Controls in the Adirondack Park [Working Draft], 1974 May (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Adirondacks, Local Planning and Land Use Controls in the Adirondack Park, A Handbook for Local Governments, 1975 September (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Adirondacks, Model On-Site Sewage Disposal Ordinance for Adirondack Park, 1979 February (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Adirondacks, Private and Public Land, Technical Report 1, Volume B, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Adirondacks, Public Hearing Draft Proposed Amendments to the Adirondack Park State Land Master Plan Text, 1978 November (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Adirondacks, Recreation, Technical Report 5, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Adirondacks, Re: Airport-Edinburg [Memo], 1995 March (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Adirondacks, Re: Model Zoning and Project Review Ordinance and Related Material, 1975 May (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Adirondacks, Re: Proposal to Improve the Economy and Environment of the Adirondack Park [Correspondence from Governor Cuomo], 1991 October (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Adirondacks, Re: Proposed Geographical Amendments to the State Land Master Plan [Memorandum], 1978 November (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Adirondacks, Re: Proposed Regulations Governing Use and Development of Adirondack River [Press Release], 1975 August (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Adirondacks, Rules and Regulations Governing the Wild, Scenic and Recreational Rivers System within the Adirondacks Park, 1976 April (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Adirondacks, Staff Draft Revision of Adirondack Park Agency Rules and Regulations [for Consultation Purposes], 1978 May (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Adirondacks, Transportation and the Economy, Technical report 4 [Temporary Study Commission on the Future of the Adirondacks Report], 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Adirondacks, Wildlife, Technical Report 2, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Appalachian Mountains, Abstract of New York State Appalachian Program: A Development Plan, 1968 October (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Appalachian Mountains, Appalachia- A Reference Book, 1979 February (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Appalachian Mountains, Appalachian Program: An Investment Plan, 1967 July (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Adirondacks, Legal Affairs Committee Daft Revision of Adirondack Park Agency Rules and Regulation [for Public Hearing Purposes], 1978 October (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Development Plan, 1971 March (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Program: A Development Plan, 1968 January (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies: Agriculture, Phase 1, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies: Agriculture, Phase 2, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies: Climate, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies, Phase 1: Community Facilities, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies: Forestry: The Timber-Based Economy, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resources Studies: Mineral Resources, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resources Studies: Recreation and Culture, Phase 1, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies: Soils, Phase 1, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resource Studies: Soil, Phase 2, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Appalachian Mountains, New York State Appalachian Resources Studies: Transportation, Phase 1: Inventory, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Appalachian Mountains, Outdoor Recreation Maps, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Adirondacks, Private and Public Land: Technical Report 1, Volume A, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Canals, The Canaler [Periodical], 1993 March-1993 June (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Canals, Canals at Cohoes Field Trip, 1980 October (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Canals, The Mighty Chain: A Guide to Canal Records in the New York State Archives, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Canals, Recreational Map and Guide to New York State Canals: Erie, Champlain, Oswego, Cayuga, Seneca [Pamphlet and Map], Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Catskills, Are the Catskills Really for Sale, A Response to the Report "The Catskills- For Sale", 1984 May (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Catskills, The Catskill Center Plan [Booklet], 1974 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Catskills, The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development [Informational Brochure], Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Catskills, The Catskills: For Sale [Report], 1984 April (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Catskills, The Future of the Catskills, Final Report by The Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills, 1975 April (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Catskills, Regionalism in the Catskills: A Political Analysis, 1979 June (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Catskills, The Role of New York City Water Supply Lands in the Catskills, Catskill Study No. 5, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Catskills, Water Resource Issues of the Catskill Region: Identification, Analysis and Recommendations, 1975 March (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Central New York, Regional Housing: An Innovative Study [Summary Report], 1971 December (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Central New York, Town of Union, Village of Johnson City and the Village of Endicott Groundwater Protection Project, 1994 September (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Columbia County, Economic Profile, 1977 September-1977 December (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Columbia County, Industrial Site Survey, 1977 June (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Columbia County, Land Use Plan, 1977 July (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Erie Canal, The Erie Canal: Clinton's $7,000,000 Ditch, 2nd Printing [Book], 1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Erie Canal, Erie Canal: Cohoes to Pattersonville Field Trip, 1988 October (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fulton County, Housing and Land Use: Summary Statement, 1978 June (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Fulton County, Human Resources Profile, 1978 March-1978 June (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Fulton County, Snow Resources, 1972 August (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Greater Region, Atlanta Region Outlook, 1989 May (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Greater Region, Northern New England Western Gateway: The East-West Highway [Re: I-88 Binghamton-Schenectady], 1970 May (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Greater Region, The Regionalist, Volume 2, Number 1 [Quarterly Journal], 1997 March-1997 June (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Greene County, Economic Profile, 1977 March-1997 June (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Greene County, Economic Study, 1972 December (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Greene County, Highway Study, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Greene County, Land Use Element, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Greene County, Power Study, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hoosic River, Classifications and Standards of Quality and Purity for Fresh Surface Water of the Hoosic River Drainage Basin, 1957 October (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hoosic River, Hoosic River Drainage Report ERRATA, 1968 December (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hudson River, Affordable Housing Challenge for the Mid-Hudson, 1987 May (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hudson River, Building Greenways in the Hudson River Valley: A Guide for Action, 1989 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hudson River, Closing the Gap-Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, Inc., 1969 May (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hudson River, Comprehensive Plan for the Abatement of Pollution from Waters of the Hudson River (Main Stream Only), 1968 December (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hudson River, Decision on the Hudson, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hudson River, Draft Study for a Hudson River Valley Greenway, 1990 April (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Hudson River, Drainage Basins of Streams Entering the Hudson River in Albany, Columbia, Greene and Rensselaer Counties: Official Classifications, 1964 February (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hudson River, Economic Profile for the Upper Hudson Region, 1973 August (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hudson River, Fenimore Bridge Over the Hudson River [Transportation Project Report], 1988 September (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hudson River, Great Lakes-Hudson River Waterway (Great Lakes to Eastern Seaboard All-American Canal), 1980 April (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hudson River, A Greenway for the Hudson River Valley - A New Strategy for Preserving an American Treasure, 1989 October (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hudson River, Greenways in the Hudson River Valley: A New Strategy for Preserving on American Treasure, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Hudson River, Historic Resources of the Hudson, 1969 January (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Hudson River, Historic Resources of the Hudson, 1969 January (Oversized 2)
  - Hudson River, Historic Sites- A Report on Historic Sites and Buildings in the Hudson River, 1965 September (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson Archeological Sites, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hudson River, Hudson Basin Project, Anatomy of an Environment: Final Report, 1976 June (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hudson River, Hudson Basin Project Occasional Paper, 1975 January (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson: Biological Resources [Hudson River Valley Commission Report], Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson: Fish and Wildlife, [Hudson River Valley Commission Report], Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson: Mineral Resources [Hudson River Valley Commission Report], Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson: The Report of the Hudson River Valley Commission, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson: Riverfront Commerce [Hudson River Valley Commission Report], Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson: Summary Report of the Hudson River Valley Commission, 1966 February (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson River Basin: Government and Natural Resources [Compiled by the League of Women Voters Education Fund], 1969 February (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Basin: Water and Related Land Resources Study, Materials for Workshop #1, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Basin: Water and Related Land Resources Study, Report on Hudson River Dialogues: Workshops #2 and #3, 1978 September-1978 October (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Basin Water and Related Land Resources Study, Selected Background Information, Technical Paper 3, Vol. 1, 1979 February (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Basin: Water and Related Land Resources Study, Technical Paper 3, Vol. 2, 1979 February (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Coastal Area: A Changing Landscape, Scenic Areas of Statewide Significance, 1990 April (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Coastal Area: A Changing Landscape, Scenic Areas of Statewide Significance, 1990 June (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Ecology [Papers from Symposium on Hudson River Ecology], 1966 October (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Ecology [Papers from Second Symposium on Hudson River Ecology], 1969 October (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hudson River, Hudson River Estuary Management Plan [Executive Summary Draft], 1990 September (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson River Lighthouses, 1967 September (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hudson River, A Hudson River Valley Greenway, 1991 February (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hudson River, The Hudson River Valley: A Heritage for All Time [Map], 1979 June (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hudson River, Hudson Valley Regional Element, New York State Coastal Management Program, 1979 March (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hudson River Valley, Land Use, Environmental Features, and Natural Resources Inventory of the Hudson River Valley [Final Report], 1969 July (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hudson River, Lower Hudson River Basin [New York State Department of Environmental Conservation Report], Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hudson River, Lower Hudson River Basin: Eastern New York River Basins Upstream Reservoir Study, Appendix A, Volume 1, 1978 May (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hudson River, Lower Hudson River Drainage Basin Survey Series Report no. 5, 1953 May (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hudson River, Lower Hudson River Drainage Basin Survey Series Report no. 11, Drainage Basins of Streams Entering the Hudson River in Albany, Columbia, Greene and Rensselaer Counties, 1962 January (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hudson River, Memorandum on Significant Fish and Wildlife Habitat Hudson River-NYC to Troy Dam, 1976 June (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hudson Valley, Mid-Hudson Industrial Survey: Manufacturing Trends in Columbia, Duchess, Greene, Orange, Putnam, Sullivan and Ulster Counties, 1970 October (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hudson River, New York City and Hudson River Waterway Use Study-New York City Area to Troy, New York, 1977 March (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hudson River, New York City and Hudson River Waterway Use Study-New York City Area to Troy, NY-Recreational Boat User Study, 1977 September (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hudson River, The Normans Kill Creek Sub-Basin, Chapter 13-11, 1977 March (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Hudson River, Power Lines and Scenic Values in the Hudson River Valley, 1968 December (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Hudson River, Proposed for Designation as a Scenic Area of Statewide Significance: Stockport/Stuyvesant, Catskill, Olana, New Baltimore/Coxsackie Scenic Areas, 1990 June (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hudson River, Proposed Revision of the Hudson River Valley Commission Rules and Regulation for Project Review, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Hudson River, Survey of the Public Administration of Water Resources in New York State [Hudson River Valley Commission Report], 1971 March (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hudson River, Upper Hudson River Drainage Basin, Except Hoosick River Drainage Basin, 1963 February (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hudson River, Upper Hudson River Drainage Basin- Official Classifications, 1965 September (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hudson River, Upper Hudson River Drainage Basin Survey Series Report No. 1, Hoosic River Drainage Basin, 1955 November (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hudson River, The Water and Related Land Resources of the Hudson Basin, Level B Study Report and Environmental Impact Statement, 1979 September (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hudson River, Water Pollution Control New York State September 1965-September 1967, The Lower Hudson and its Tributaries, 1967 September (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hudson River, Water Quality Management Plan for Planning Area 11-02 [Draft], 1977 March (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hudson Valley, The Mid-Hudson: A Development Guide, 1973 (Oversized 2)
  - Mohawk Valley, Composition and Needs of the Mohawk Valley Workforce, 1991 May (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mohawk Valley, Comprehensive Economic Development Strategy for the Mohawk Valley Economic Development District, Inc., 1978 October (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mohawk Valley, Comprehensive Plan for the Abatement of Pollution from Waters of the Mohawk River Drainage Basin, Except Sauquoit Creek, West Canada Creek, East Canada Creek, and Schoharie Creek, 1968 December (Box 5, Folder 10)